the way the econom is moving whether
it's electric vehicles whether it's
digital platforms whether it's
Electronics manufacturing right all
these requires uh that the chip industry
to to to ruction of chips so I think
India is taking veryy steps they're
starting with the osat assembling and
testing part and their big Investments
announced I think it's a it's a good
beginning and it's very much required
for uh for the policy makers Vision to
come through that India will be
exporting billion worth of electronics
uh from India without a chip making base
that targets will not be met so it's
very important uh to have that uh to uh
to to make a beginning on that the
concern that I uh discovered in covering
the early stages of the early phases of
this seventh phase election is that
there may be a risk that Narendra Modi
may not get a Mega majority is that
going to
undermine the economic agenda and
undermine this momentum towards
digitizing the economy sure I think uh
there are digitizing economy is a is a
separate LEL I think digitizing economy
formalizing the economy was actually
started in 2011 of course PM Modi has
accelerated the process but now digital
identity uh the formal economy is very
well in the motion that cannot be
reversed however I think two policy
choices I think this government has very
decisively made one was in favor of
fiscal consolidation so therefore the
fiscal deficit down from 9% in 2021 to
5% this year and second to increase cfex
to GDP so cax G is gone from 2% to 3 and
a half% right now so these are two very
delivered policy choices made by this
government and also this the subsidies
or the incentives for semiconductors and
other things that you're talking about
also delivered Poli
choices should this policy making uh
become you know uh there is some sort of
issue with not getting majority of
course we you know there could be some
volatility around that but our BAS case
remains that they will not get mega
majority but the current uh
administration and policy should
continue